lorisshoes.com 2019-04-20

# Terms of Use & Privacy Policy

### HOW DO I KNOW MY INFORMATION IS KEPT PRIVATE?

This Privacy Statement describes how we collect and use your information and gives you options as to how your information is used. We suggest you review this Privacy Statement periodically, as we may update it from time to time. We post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Skye Associates, LLC. Any communication or material sent to you will be considered confidential and will become the property of Skye Associates, LLC which reserves the right to use and reproduce it for any purpose whatsoever. Access and use of the Site is subject to the terms, conditions and applicable laws construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Maryland. When you purchase from our site, we collect information that you volunteer, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number and other information necessary to process your order. Periodically we will send you email about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events ONLY if you have elected to receive these mailings. We also collect information you provide us when you register to participate in a contest or promotion, fill out a survey or questionnaire, or contact us.

### HOW DO I KNOW MY INFORMATION IS SECURE?

We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site, so you can feel comfortable and secure when shopping. When you see either a solid key icon or a locked padlock icon at the lower portion of your browser window, the site is secured through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving your personal information on our site. Pages requesting personal information should always have one of these icons.

### WHAT ARE 'COOKIES' AND HOW DO WE USE THEM?

A "cookie" is a small data file that contains a unique identifier. Cookies can be used to store personal information about you on your computer. The cookie ensures that only the computer used to select items will have access to products you have chosen and billing information you've entered. Using a cookie is the safest way to make sure that only you can see the contents of your shopping cart and order form.

LorisShoes.com does not believe in storing your personal information on a cookie. This is not a responsible use of this information. We do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information. We guarantee that your data is not used for any other purpose than improving our web site and overall shopping experience.

### CAN I COPY ANYTHING FROM THE SITE?

By law, the material displayed on the site may not be downloaded for anything other than non-commercial and personal use, and then only if copyright and other proprietary notices contained on the materials are retained.

All images on LorisShoes.com are readily available in various places on the internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the US Copyright Fair Use Act.

If you believe that any content appearing on LorisShoes.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know … and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.

### AND...LAST BUT NOT LEAST...

By accessing and using this site, you submit to the jurisdiction of the Federal District Court for the District Court of Maryland and accept all terms and conditions without limitation or qualification. Everything on this site is copyrighted unless otherwise noted, and may not be used without the written permission of lorisshoes.com. Images of people, places, buttons and items displayed on the site are either the property of, or used with permission by, lorisshoes.com. The use of these images is prohibited unless specifically permitted by lorisshoes.com. Any unauthorized use of the images may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes. In addition, archiving, redistribution, re-publication or derivation of any information contained or downloaded from this site, in any medium, including but not limited to electronic, CD-ROM, or database, or publication in print, requires the written consent of lorisshoes.com. The trademarks, the logo and all the published names displayed on the site are the property of lorisshoes.com. Nothing contained on the site should be construed as granting any license or right to use any trademarks displayed on the site without the written permission of its owners. Use of the trademarks or other materials displayed on the site is completely prohibited.
